{
    "id": "932af31163084f2382c573167137990d",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ………………… the admission card. I ……………… it two days ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "received, received",
                "have received, received",
                "had received, received"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. the fee. I ……………….. it only yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "paid, paid",
                "have paid, paid",
                "had paid, paid"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My uncle …………….. from the States. He ……………… on Friday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "came, arrived",
                "has come, arrived",
                "has come, had arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think I will pass the test. I …………….. only nine questions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "answered",
                "had answered",
                "have answered"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………… non-vegetarian food.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "never tasted",
                "have never tasted",
                "had never tasted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. my aunt two months ago. I …………….. her since then.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have visited, have not seen",
                "visited, have not seen",
                "visited, had not seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………….. the construction two months ago, but we ……………… in only two weeks ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have completed, have moved",
                "completed, have moved",
                "completed, moved"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When Rama ………………. to the forest, Sita and Lakshmana ……………….. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has gone, accompanied",
                "had gone, accompanied",
                "went, accompanied"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. ill last month. He ……………. as yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fell, has not recovered",
                "has fallen, had not recovered",
                "had fallen, has not recovered"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… my aunt only once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "see",
                "have seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}